(Penny:)Look, Leonard, you have to know
how much I care about you.
(Penny:)It's just that I've said the L word
too soon before...
(Penny:)...and it didn't work out very well.
(Raj:)Really?
I wouldn't know what that's like.
(Penny:)I'm sorry.
(Raj:)-You know what I'm talking about.
-Yeah, I do.
(Penny:)-So we're good?
-Yes, that's what I'm telling you.
(Leonard:)We are good. We are great.
All right. Fence mended,
problem swept under the rug.
(Sheldon:)Time to bowl.
(Sheldon:)Yes, I was eavesdropping.
There's a lot at stake.
(Sheldon:)Attention, all bowlers...
(Sheldon:)...I've taken the liberty
of having these made for our rematch.
(Penny:)-The Wesley Crushers?
-No, not the Wesley Crushers.
The Wesley "Crushers."
(Penny:)-I don't get it.
-Wesley Crusher...
(Leonard:)...was Wil Wheaton's character
on Star Trek.
(Penny:)Still don't get it.
(Sheldon:)It's a blindingly clever play on words.
(Sheldon:)By appropriating his character's
name and adding the S...